Finding Aid for Center for Global and Intercultural Study (University of Michigan) publications, 1964-1995
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
Center for Global and Intercultural Study (University of Michigan) publications 1964-1995
University of Michigan. Center for Global and Intercultural Study.
0392 Bimu 2
Publications produced by or for Center for Global and Intercultural Study (formerly Office of International Programs); includes brochures, bulletins, and newsletters which describe the various international study programs available to University of Michigan students.
0.5 linear feet
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
Publications are received periodically from the unit (donor no. 8099 )
Periodic additions to the records expected.
The publications are open without restriction.
For historical sketch see finding aid for Center for Global and Intercultural Study (University of Michigan) records.
The Publications (0.5 linear feet), includes brochures, bulletins, and newsletters which describe the various international study programs available to University of Michigan students
Subjects:
University of Michigan. Office of International Programs.
Genre Terms:
Pamphlets.; Newsletters.
- General Unit Publications
  The General Unit Publications contain publications about the Office of International Programs. The Individual Program Publications include publications which describe the various international study programs available to University of Michigan students.
  - Brochures 1985-1995 (Box 1)
  - Newsletters
    - Notes from the Office of International Programs 1995 (Box 1)
- Individual Program Publications
  - Academic Year Exchange Program
    - Tubingen, Germany
      - Brochures 1985-1995 (Box 1)
    - University of Lausanne, Switzerland
      - Brochures 1995 (Box 1)
    - University of Turku, Finland
      - Brochures 1995 (Box 1)
    - University of Western Australia
      - Brochures 1994 (Box 1)
    - Uppsala University, Sweden
      - Brochures 1995 (Box 1)
  - Academic Year Program
    - Aix-en-Provence, France
      - Brochures 1989-1994 (Box 1)
    - Florence, Italy
      - Brochures 1983-1996 (Box 1)
      - Bulletins 1989-1993 (Box 1)
    - Japan
      - Brochures 1995-1996 (Box 1)
    - Quito, Ecuador
      - Brochures 1995 (Box 1)
    - Santiago, Chile
      - Brochures 1995 (Box 1)
    - Seoul, Korea
      - Brochures 1995 (Box 1)
    - Seville, Spain
      - Brochures 1990-1995 (Box 1)
    - Tianjin and Beijing, China
      - Brochures 1995 (Box 1)
  - American Collegiate Consortium Exchange Program
    - Former Soviet Union and Baltic Countries
      - Brochures 1995 (Box 1)
  - Committee on Institutional Cooperation
    - Internship Program
      - Australia
        - Brochures 1995 (Box 1)
      - London
        - Brochures 1995 (Box 1)
  - Summer Study Program
    - Dominican Republic
      - Brochures 1995 (Box 1)
    - Quebec
      - Brochures 1995 (Box 1)
  - Intercollegiate Center for Classical Studies
    - Rome
      - Brochures 1995 (Box 1)
  - International Summer Session
    - Uppsala, Sweden
      - Brochures 1995 (Box 1)
  - Junior Year
    - Edinburgh
      - Brochures undated (Box 1)
    - France
      - Aix-en-Provence
        - Brochures undated, 1969/70 (Box 1)
      - Bulletins
        - Guide des Cours, 1984-1985 (Box 1)
      - Manuals
        - Student Handbook, 1982-1983 (Box 1)
    - Freiburg
      - Brochures, 1992/1993 1995 (Box 1)
      - Bulletins 1964-1995, 3 folders (Box 1)
      - Newsletters
        - Alumni Newsletter 1986-1989 (Box 1)
    - Munich
      - Bulletins 1983-1984, 1993-1994 (Box 1)
  - National Trust for Historic Preservation
    - Florence
      - Brochures 1984-1986 (Box 1)
  - Programs at British Universities
    - Brochures 1989-1995 (Box 1)
  - Smithsonian Associates Travel Program
    - Florence
      - Bulletins 1984-1986 (Box 1)
  - Summer Language Program
    - Saint-Malo
      - Brochures 1989-1994 (Box 1)
  - Summer Study Program
    - Dublin
      - Brochures 1995 (Box 1)
    - Florence and London
      - Brochures 1973-1985 (Box 1)
    - Jamaica
      - Brochures 1995 (Box 1)
    - London
      - Brochures 1989-1995 (Box 1)
    - Mexico, University of Guanajuato
      - Brochures 1995 (Box 1)
    - Oxford University
      - Brochures 1989-1995 (Box 1)
    - Salamanca, Spain
      - Brochures undated, 1995 (Box 1)
    - Seville and Madrid
      - Brochures 1989-1990 (Box 1)
    - Southern France
      - Bulletins undated (Box 1)